dailygalaxy.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy | The Daily Galaxy

## The Daily Galaxy Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At the Daily Galaxy, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

This Privacy Policy governs your use of dailygalaxy.com

We automatically receive and record certain personal data of yours when you visit our websites. This includes device model, IP address, the type of browser and operating system being used.

When you sign up to any of our service(s) such as our Disqus Comments platform, we may collect your contact information such as name, e-mail address, unique identifiers, such as nick names and passwords.

To enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.

 **Children**

Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

 **Third-party advertisements**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site or mobile application. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

 **Audience measurement**

We use third party tools for audience measurement on our websites. We currently use Google Analytics and Quantcast for this purpose. Google Analytics and Quantcast uses cookies to anonymously and in aggregate report on visits to our websites. We do not combine the information collected through the use of these tools with personally identifiable information. Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at www.google.com/analytics/terms. The Quantcast privacy policy is available at www.quantcast.com/privacy

 **Linked web sites**

We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites.

 **Questions?**

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
